<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../ph.xsl"?>

<page>
  <title><b>CRUMS Puzzle of the Month!</b></title>
  <content>
    <section>
    <h2><u>CRUMS 2 – November 2016</u></h2>
    <p>
	<b>Constructor:</b> Zach B. <br />
	<b>Date/Time:</b> Sunday, November 20 at 2 PM <br />
	<b># of Puzzles:</b> 6 and a meta <br />
	<b>Team Size:</b> ~2-3 <br />
    </p>
    <p>
	<b>Details:</b> At 2 PM, all puzzles except the meta will be released. As soon as any team reaches 4 
	solves, the metapuzzle becomes unlocked for all teams. Each team may submit up to 25 guesses during the hunt. No hints will ever be released. 
	Every puzzle, including the meta, is worth 1 point. The first team to reach 7 points is declared the winner. The hunt officially ends at 5 PM, 
	but the site (including the answer checker) will stay live after the hunt is over. 
	All teams that complete the meta are entitled to a small prize, as a token of my appreciation
	for solving these puzzles. 
    </p>
    <p>
	So... find a partner or two and register a team. Or go it alone.
    </p>
    <p>
	<b>The next POTM will be constructed by:</b> [unclaimed]
    </p>
    </section>
    <section>
      <h2><u>General Information</u></h2>
      <h3>What is CRUMS?</h3>
      <p>
        CRUMS is a monthly, rotating puzzle event maintained by a small community of puzzle enthusiaists loosely affiliated with Brown University.
      </p>

      <h3>How does it work?</h3>
      <p>
        At a certain time each month, a puzzle or small batch of puzzles will be released. 
	The next month, someone else – possibly the previous winner – takes over the puzzle-constructing duties. 
	In addition, each puzzle is test-solved / edited by the previous month's writer(s).
      </p>

      <h3>When do the puzzles go live?</h3>
      <p>
        TBA. Ideally, the puzzles will go live at a set time each month, much like the <a href="http://shinteki.com/potm">Shinteki POTM</a>. As of yet, no time
	has been determined.
      </p>

      <h3>Acknowledgments</h3>
      <p>
        CRUMS owes its existence to Alex Walker and Sara Schulz, who together wrote the first ever CRUMS Puzzlehunt. This spiffy site is the product of
	blood, sweat, and tears extracted from Justin Pombrio and Vikram Saraph. It's a good thing grad students can't unionize!
      </p>

      <h3>What does 'CRUMS' stand for?</h3>
      <p>
	¯\_(ツ)_/¯
      </p>
    </section>
  </content>
</page>
