<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="../ph.xsl"?>

<page>
  <title>CRUMS Puzzle Hunt, 2016</title>
  <subtitle>Alex Walker &amp; Sara Schulz</subtitle>
  <content>
    <section>
      <h3>What is CRUMS?</h3>
      <p>
        CRUMS is a small puzzle hunt created by a couple of crazy
        people in Providence, RI, one of whom is affiliated with Brown
        University. They felt that there weren't enough puzzle hunts
        in the world, so they made their own.
      </p>

      <h3>When is CRUMS?</h3>
      <p>
        CRUMS will kick off on Saturday, 9/24 at noon EST (that's 2:00
        a.m. on Sunday in Australian time).  Puzzles and hints will be
        released during the subsequent 30 hours.  The last hints will
        be released on Sunday, 9/25 at 2:00 p.m., and the hunt will
        officially conclude at 6:00 p.m.  The puzzles will remain
        online indefinitely, though, so don't worry if you're a bit
        late to the party.
      </p>

      <h3>Where is CRUMS?</h3>
      <p>
        The internet!  Speaking of parties, though, there will be an
        afterparty on Sunday, 9/25 at 7:00 p.m.  There will be
        delicious snacks, and you'll be able to compare notes (or
        commiserate) with your fellow puzzlers.  You'll receive the
        location of the party when you register; it's at our
        apartment, so please don't post the location online or invite
        anyone you don't actually know.
      </p>

      <h3>How is CRUMS?</h3>
      <p>
        We think it's pretty sweet!  That said, we're excited to hear
        your feedback after the hunt is over to help make future
        iterations go more smoothly.
      </p>

      <h3>Who is CRUMS?</h3>
      <p>
        This has gone on long enough.  Let's get back to the real
        questions.
      </p>

      <h3>How do I participate in CRUMS?</h3>
      <p>
        Assemble a team of up to 4 people and register on this very
        website.  Create a team name and password (that you can
        remember!) that you will all use to submit answers.
      </p>

      <h3>What's in it for me?</h3>
      <p>
        In addition to the honor of writing the next CRUMS hunt, the
        team with the most points at the end of the hunt will receive
        a prize at our highly exclusive afterparty!  If you can't make
        it to the afterparty, we'll be deeply disappointed, but we'll
        find a way to get you your prize.
      </p>

      <h3>What is the scoring system like?</h3>
      <p>
        Each puzzle (except the meta) will be worth a maximum of 3
        points, minus 1 point for each hint that has been released.
        The meta will be worth 10 points, but there will not be any
        hints for it.  Confused?  Check out this sweet table:

        <table>
          <tr>
            <th>Puzzle type</th>
            <th>#Hints</th>
            <th>Points</th>
          </tr>
          <tr>
            <td>Non-meta</td>
            <td>0</td>
            <td>3</td>
          </tr>
          <tr>
            <td>Non-meta</td>
            <td>1</td>
            <td>2</td>
          </tr>
          <tr>
            <td>Non-meta</td>
            <td>2</td>
            <td>1</td>
          </tr>
          <tr>
            <td>Meta</td>
            <td>0</td>
            <td>10</td>
          </tr>
        </table>
      </p>
      <p>
        *Ties will be broken based on average solve time
      </p>

      <h3>Anything else?</h3>
      <p>
        We don't think so, but if you do have a question that isn't
        answered here, please feel free to drop us a line at <a
        href="mailto:contact@crumspuzzlehunt.com">contact@crumspuzzlehunt.com</a>.
        Good luck and have fun!
      </p>
    </section>
  </content>
</page>
